[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Wolf"]}, "docId": "120121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 18, "question": "Piers?", "question_tokens": ["Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 19, "answer": "I certainly am, Wolf.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "certainly", "am", ",", "Wolf", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "How do you feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "Oh, we're very excited.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "we", "'re", "very", "excited", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "But how did you feel, on a personal level, to see such an incredibly personal interview attacking your father in that way?", "question_tokens": ["But", "how", "did", "you", "feel", ",", "on", "a", "personal", "level", ",", "to", "see", "such", "an", "incredibly", "personal", "interview", "attacking", "your", "father", "in", "that", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Well, we haven't -- I haven't actually seen it, but I can tell you that, of course, in these times, when it is heated, things come out of the blue.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "have", "n't", "--", "I", "have", "n't", "actually", "seen", "it", ",", "but", "I", "can", "tell", "you", "that", ",", "of", "course", ",", "in", "these", "times", ",", "when", "it", "is", "heated", ",", "things", "come", "out", "of", "the", "blue", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "Do you feel that he really is genuinely a different man now to the man that he was maybe in his 30s and 40s?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "that", "he", "really", "is", "genuinely", "a", "different", "man", "now", "to", "the", "man", "that", "he", "was", "maybe", "in", "his", "30s", "and", "40s", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", "CC", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "Who are you targeting?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "are", "you", "targeting", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "I love the way you framed that question.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "the", "way", "you", "framed", "that", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Florida"]}, "docId": "120121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "What do you think his strategy will be in Florida?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "his", "strategy", "will", "be", "in", "Florida", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "Well, I happen to be from Florida now.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "happen", "to", "be", "from", "Florida", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Florida"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["January 31st"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["Florida"]}, "docId": "120121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "CC", "NNP", "CD", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "Everything has changed, hasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Everything", "has", "changed", ",", "has", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "It certainly has, and I think there's no doubt, I think it's going to be a race because Florida, you know, 10 days between now and January 31st, Piers, a lot could happen.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "certainly", "has", ",", "and", "I", "think", "there", "'s", "no", "doubt", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "a", "race", "because", "Florida", ",", "you", "know", ",", "10", "days", "between", "now", "and", "January", "31st", ",", "Piers", ",", "a", "lot", "could", "happen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "Maybe not, though, the end of the story by a long way, because Florida is looming large in everything, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Maybe", "not", ",", "though", ",", "the", "end", "of", "the", "story", "by", "a", "long", "way", ",", "because", "Florida", "is", "looming", "large", "in", "everything", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "Yes, I think the beauty is we have 50 states that are very different.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "think", "the", "beauty", "is", "we", "have", "50", "states", "that", "are", "very", "different", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Florida"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Newt Gingrich", "Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "120121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 259, "question": "Do you really think that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "really", "think", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "Yes, it's absolutely true, I think there's no question that Newt Gingrich cannot beat Barack Obama.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "'s", "absolutely", "true", ",", "I", "think", "there", "'s", "no", "question", "that", "Newt", "Gingrich", "can", "not", "beat", "Barack", "Obama", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "Where does that leave you?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "does", "that", "leave", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "Well, actually, this was about the second best night we could have.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "actually", ",", "this", "was", "about", "the", "second", "best", "night", "we", "could", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iowa"]}, "docId": "120121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "It's like a domino effect, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "like", "a", "domino", "effect", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "Well, the real interesting thing about Iowa was that we spent by far the least amount of money and, as we know, officially yesterday won it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "real", "interesting", "thing", "about", "Iowa", "was", "that", "we", "spent", "by", "far", "the", "least", "amount", "of", "money", "and", ",", "as", "we", "know", ",", "officially", "yesterday", "won", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "DT", "IN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "At what point do you think you would reach that moment if you had to?", "question_tokens": ["At", "what", "point", "do", "you", "think", "you", "would", "reach", "that", "moment", "if", "you", "had", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "Well, let's put this in context, first of all.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "let", "'s", "put", "this", "in", "context", ",", "first", "of", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "If he ends up in a position where he could be a running mate to either Newt Gingrich or Mitt Romney, and I accept you're not going to throw the towel in -- he may -- he may yet go on to win it -- but would he be prepared to be a running mate to either or both of those candidates?", "question_tokens": ["If", "he", "ends", "up", "in", "a", "position", "where", "he", "could", "be", "a", "running", "mate", "to", "either", "Newt", "Gingrich", "or", "Mitt", "Romney", ",", "and", "I", "accept", "you", "'re", "not", "going", "to", "throw", "the", "towel", "in", "--", "he", "may", "--", "he", "may", "yet", "go", "on", "to", "win", "it", "--", "but", "would", "he", "be", "prepared", "to", "be", "a", "running", "mate", "to", "either", "or", "both", "of", "those", "candidates", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ":", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "Not even looking at that right now.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "even", "looking", "at", "that", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Newt Gingrich", "Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Sunday"], "ORGANIZATION": ["NFL"]}, "docId": "120121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NNP", "RB", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "What are you expecting to happen in Florida?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "expecting", "to", "happen", "in", "Florida", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "Well, I think, you know, it's like in the NFL, they say on any given Sunday now with -- we're down to the Final Four, these are all professionals, they've got great resumes, they know what they're doing.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", ",", "you", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "like", "in", "the", "NFL", ",", "they", "say", "on", "any", "given", "Sunday", "now", "with", "--", "we", "'re", "down", "to", "the", "Final", "Four", ",", "these", "are", "all", "professionals", ",", "they", "'ve", "got", "great", "resumes", ",", "they", "know", "what", "they", "'re", "doing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Florida"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "What are you hearing?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "hearing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "I'm -- yes, the stories that I'm hearing, what I'm reading is that he's not planning on endorsing.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "--", "yes", ",", "the", "stories", "that", "I", "'m", "hearing", ",", "what", "I", "'m", "reading", "is", "that", "he", "'s", "not", "planning", "on", "endorsing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "120121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Why do you think that happened?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "think", "that", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "Well, I think people are most of all looking to see a candidate that can defeat Barack Obama, that are thinking about supporting the Republican candidate for presidency.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "people", "are", "most", "of", "all", "looking", "to", "see", "a", "candidate", "that", "can", "defeat", "Barack", "Obama", ",", "that", "are", "thinking", "about", "supporting", "the", "Republican", "candidate", "for", "presidency", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Newt Gingrich", "Chris Christie", "Donald Trump"]}, "docId": "120121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "RP", "RB", "CC", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "Do you believe that was a -- really a turning point for dealing with that kind of baggage?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "that", "was", "a", "--", "really", "a", "turning", "point", "for", "dealing", "with", "that", "kind", "of", "baggage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBD", "DT", ":", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "REITBART: We've got a situation here where Newt Gingrich, right now, before that, you had Chris Christie, Donald Trump, any candidate that goes out there and attacks the mainstream media immediately gains 20 points amongst conservatives.", "answer_tokens": ["REITBART", ":", "We", "'ve", "got", "a", "situation", "here", "where", "Newt", "Gingrich", ",", "right", "now", ",", "before", "that", ",", "you", "had", "Chris", "Christie", ",", "Donald", "Trump", ",", "any", "candidate", "that", "goes", "out", "there", "and", "attacks", "the", "mainstream", "media", "immediately", "gains", "20", "points", "amongst", "conservatives", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "Yes, but I mean, Amy Holmes, let me bring you in here because I suppose another way of looking at this, in a White House way, is that this is all quite good for Barack Obama, because you've got the heavyweights of the Republican Party right now just taking seven lumps out of each other every two seconds, negative ad, negative ad, all this stuff accumulates and becomes, I would imagine, a rather useful punch bag for Barack Obama when he works out who the nominee is going to be, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "I", "mean", ",", "Amy", "Holmes", ",", "let", "me", "bring", "you", "in", "here", "because", "I", "suppose", "another", "way", "of", "looking", "at", "this", ",", "in", "a", "White", "House", "way", ",", "is", "that", "this", "is", "all", "quite", "good", "for", "Barack", "Obama", ",", "because", "you", "'ve", "got", "the", "heavyweights", "of", "the", "Republican", "Party", "right", "now", "just", "taking", "seven", "lumps", "out", "of", "each", "other", "every", "two", "seconds", ",", "negative", "ad", ",", "negative", "ad", ",", "all", "this", "stuff", "accumulates", "and", "becomes", ",", "I", "would", "imagine", ",", "a", "rather", "useful", "punch", "bag", "for", "Barack", "Obama", "when", "he", "works", "out", "who", "the", "nominee", "is", "going", "to", "be", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "DT", "CD", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "CC", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"], "PERSON": ["Amy Holmes", "Barack Obama", "Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "Look at Mitt Romney, reacting to, are you going to let us see your taxes?", "question_tokens": ["Look", "at", "Mitt", "Romney", ",", "reacting", "to", ",", "are", "you", "going", "to", "let", "us", "see", "your", "taxes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "TO", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "He looked weak on that.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "looked", "weak", "on", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last three years"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Tea Party", "Tea Party", "Tea Party"], "PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "RB", ",", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "RP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "Andrew Breitbart, come in there, because that's a good point, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Andrew", "Breitbart", ",", "come", "in", "there", ",", "because", "that", "'s", "a", "good", "point", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "IN", "EX", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "Whether Mitt Romney wants to accept it or not, this -- the last three years was the era of the ascendancy of the Tea Party and he's done everything he can to say, well, I -- he likes to parrot Tea Party phrases and Tea Party ideas that are out there only because of the Tea Party , but he wants to distance himself from the people that were maligned by the media.", "answer_tokens": ["Whether", "Mitt", "Romney", "wants", "to", "accept", "it", "or", "not", ",", "this", "--", "the", "last", "three", "years", "was", "the", "era", "of", "the", "ascendancy", "of", "the", "Tea", "Party", "and", "he", "'s", "done", "everything", "he", "can", "to", "say", ",", "well", ",", "I", "--", "he", "likes", "to", "parrot", "Tea", "Party", "phrases", "and", "Tea", "Party", "ideas", "that", "are", "out", "there", "only", "because", "of", "the", "Tea", "Party", ",", "but", "he", "wants", "to", "distance", "himself", "from", "the", "people", "that", "were", "maligned", "by", "the", "media", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Andrew Breitbart"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1994"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Piers", "U.S. Senate"], "PERSON": ["Edward Kennedy", "Edward Kennedy"]}, "docId": "120121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "CD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "RP", ",", "IN", "NN", "EX", "VBD", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "Where is he going wrong in selling this message?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "is", "he", "going", "wrong", "in", "selling", "this", "message", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Well, Piers, it's interesting, because we go back in his history to 1994 when he ran for the U.S. Senate against Edward Kennedy, a lot of the same issues came up, for example there were ads run by the Edward Kennedy campaign against him, saying that he was killing jobs.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "it", "'s", "interesting", ",", "because", "we", "go", "back", "in", "his", "history", "to", "1994", "when", "he", "ran", "for", "the", "U.S.", "Senate", "against", "Edward", "Kennedy", ",", "a", "lot", "of", "the", "same", "issues", "came", "up", ",", "for", "example", "there", "were", "ads", "run", "by", "the", "Edward", "Kennedy", "campaign", "against", "him", ",", "saying", "that", "he", "was", "killing", "jobs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "RB", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "I mean, there are two ways in looking at what they did, aren't there?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "there", "are", "two", "ways", "in", "looking", "at", "what", "they", "did", ",", "are", "n't", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "There always are, Piers, and I think the problem is that the American public doesn't understand finance very well.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "always", "are", ",", "Piers", ",", "and", "I", "think", "the", "problem", "is", "that", "the", "American", "public", "does", "n't", "understand", "finance", "very", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "Why isn't he showing more passion?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "n't", "he", "showing", "more", "passion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VBG", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "I think one of the big problems for him is the Occupy movement.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "one", "of", "the", "big", "problems", "for", "him", "is", "the", "Occupy", "movement", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]